fullcontactpoker.com 2013-05-21

# Full Contact Poker : Your online poker community

This policy covers how FullContactPoker.com treats personal information that FullContactPoker.com collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable, like your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number, and that  
is not otherwise publicly available.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that FullContactPoker.com does not control.

FullContactPoker.com collects personal information when you register with FullContactPoker.com, when you use FullContactPoker.com products or services, when you visit FullContactPoker.com pages or the pages of certain FullContactPoker.com partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. FullContactPoker.com may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register, we ask for information such as your name, e-mail address, birth date, gender, zip code, and personal interests. Once you register with FullContactPoker.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

FullContactPoker.com collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners.

FullContactPoker.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, FullContactPoker.com cookie information, and the page you request.

FullContactPoker.com uses information for the following general purposes: to facilitate the forums, offer exclusive opportunities to a select membership group, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

FullContactPoker.com would share personal information about you under the following circumstances:

• We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;  
• We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law.  
• We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with FullContactPoker.com under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help FullContactPoker.com communicate with you about  
offers from FullContactPoker.com and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.  
• If FullContactPoker.com should ever file for bankruptcy, or become insolvent, or be acquired by a third party, merge with a third party, sell all or part of Our assets, or transfer substantially all or part of Our relevant assets to a third party, FullContactPoker.com is entitled to share the Personal Information and all other information you have provided through the Service to potential and subsequent  
business and merger partners.

FullContactPoker.com may set and access FullContactPoker.com cookies on your computer.

Cookies are anonymous .txt files that allow us to remember you and your preferences from previous visits. FullContactPoker.com cookies collect no personally identifiable information.

FullContactPoker.com may update this policy and would update the significant changes on our website.

Effective Date: This policy was last updated on May 29th 2007
